





SUMMARY

Qualified and professional with three years of experience in building responsive websites. Proficient in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, WordPress, and other web development technologies including React. Strong problem-solving skills and a passion for staying up-to-date with the latest web development trends and technologies. Ability to work effectively in a team-based environment.

SKILLS

- °HTML
- CSS
- Javascript
- Bootstrap
- SASS
- Tailwind CSS
- React
- WordPress/Elementor
- Duda

- Visual Studio
- GitHub
- Subscription Management System

WORK EXPERIENCE

Digital Laboratory Company

Web Developer • 2019 - 2022

- Collaborated with web designer and director to identify and prioritize features and requirements of site development
- Worked with Figma designs and created browser-friendly sites using WordPress and Duda
- Maintained and monitored website performance and improved according to Google Speed Insights
- Cooperated within Agile teams and utilized Scrum methodologies, as well as tools like Atlassian JIRA
- Tested and implemented subscription management platforms such as Chargebee, Zoho Subscription, and WooCommerce for our in-house service websites
- Tested Zoho CRM automation process for plan subscription and collaborated with website

Data Link Technology

Web Developer Intern • 2018 - 2018

- Collaborated with senior developers to develop and maintain hands-on project using Wordpress, HTML,CSS,JavaScript
- Conducted code reviews and fixed feedbacks to improve code quality

PROJECTS

Portfolio website

React, React Hooks, JavaScript, CSS, Framer Motion

Clone website

React, Redux, JavaScript, Libraries

Certification projects

React, Redux, React Hooks, JavaScript, SASS

Learning & practicing

React, Redux, React Hooks, JavaScript, SASS

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Computer Engineering & Information Technology

Mandalay Technical University • 2012-2018

CERTIFICATIONS

Front End Development Libraries

freeCodeCamp.org

Javascript/ React+Redux

<u>sololearn</u>